听着  先生  我最后一次告诉你
Listen, you know what, sir, for the last time,
我不管电脑上登记了什么
I don't care what the computer says.
我们没从房间冰箱拿走一包糖果
We did not take a bag of Mashuga Nuts from the minibar.
我们也没看《热心"助"人的医生》
And we did not watch Dr. Do-Me-A-Little.
-乔伊  昨晚你到过我们房间吗  -没有
- Joey, were you in our room last night? - No.
他们说电影片名不会出现在帐单上
I was told the name of the movie would not appear on the bill.
我们要退掉新婚套房
We're checking out of the bridal suite.
没错  我不再是新娘了
That's right, I'm no longer a bride.
也永远都当不了新娘
I'll never be a bride again.
现在我不过是某人的太太
Now I'm just someone's wife.
而我是全世界最幸福的男人
And I'm the happiest guy in the world.
亲爱的  别难过
Come on. Honey, don't be upset.
-我们的未来充满期待  -可不是嘛
- We still have so much to look forward to. - Yeah, right.
我们还要去度蜜月
We got the honeymoon.
那还要等到星期四
That's not till Thursday.
还有婚纱照
The wedding pictures.
那得等上好几个星期
It won't be ready for weeks.
但婚宴上用"即可拍"拍的照片马上可以洗好
Not the disposable cameras from the tables.
没错  我就知道我嫁给你是有原因的
That's true. I knew I married you for a reason!
听着  我拿照片去洗  你先回家吧
Tell you what, I will go get them developed, and you can go home.
好
Okay.
-怎么  你拍了什么  -没什么
- What? What did you take a picture of? - Nothing.
绝对精彩哦
It was something.
即可拍在罗斯那里  他还没有退房吗
Ross has the cameras. Has he checked out yet?
你开什么玩笑  退房时间是中午
Are you joking? Checkout is not till noon.
-他还有11分钟  -所以呢
- And he has a good 11 minutes left. - So?
罗斯从来不会提早退房  一分钟都不浪费
So Ross had never checked out of a room a minute before he had to.
我们在交往的时候  有一次延后退房
One time, when we were dating, we got a late checkout.
他异常兴奋  那是我们最性福的一次
He got so excited, it was the best sex we ever had.
结果他最后大喊"雷迪森酒店"  真扫兴
Until he screamed out "Radisson" at the end.
好吧  我去找罗斯拿照相机
Okay, well, I'm gonna get Ross, get the cameras
然后把底片拿去洗
and get them developed.
乔伊  你都32岁了  别那么幼稚行吗
32, Joe. You're 32!
-这是你的帐单  -谢谢
- Here's a copy of your bill. - Thanks.
香槟  草莓...
Champagne, strawberries...
天啊
Oh, my God!
我不敢相信钱德勒在我们的新婚之夜看黄片
I can't believe Chandler ordered porn on our wedding night.
对  真可悲
Yeah, that's sad.
来点糖果吧
Mashuga Nut?
肥皂  洗发水  你真的要带这些东西吗
Soaps, shampoos. Are you really taking all this stuff?
为什么不行  这全包含在房费里
Why not? It's built into the price of the room.
对  但你不需要...  这是什么
Yeah, but you don't need... What is this?
针线包
Thread.
答对了
Score!
即可拍在哪里
Where are the disposable cameras?
什么即可拍
What disposable cameras?
昨晚我把它们交给你保管
The cameras. Remember last night I asked you to take them.
-才没有  -怎么没有  记得吗
- No, you didn't. - Yes, remember?
在切蛋糕前  我找到你说...
Right before we cut the cake, I went up to you and I said...
对  你问我能不能帮你一个忙
Yeah, you asked me if I could do you a favor.
这时墨瑞叔叔走过来交给你一张支票
Then my Uncle Murray came up to you and handed you a check.
然后你问"它为什么叫做支票
Then you said, "Why is it called a check?
为什么不叫南斯拉夫人"
Why not a Yugoslavian?"
对  然后你笑得魂不附体
Yeah, then you did that,
-即可拍不在你手上  -没错  抱歉
- So you don't have the cameras? - No, sorry, man.
那怎么办  相机不见了  莫妮卡会气疯的
So, what? They're gone? Monica's gonna freak!
它们应该就在酒店里某个地方
I'm sure they're somewhere here in the hotel.
我帮你找
I'll help you look for that.
-太棒了  -再等三分钟
- Great. - In three minutes.
你要丢下钱德勒  自己拆礼物吗
Are you gonna open the presents without Chandler?
不  我只是
No! I'm just...
它们在呼换我
They're calling out to me.
这个小家伙甚至都爬到我大腿上了
This little guy even crawled up in my lap.
我就拆一样礼物  钱德勒不会介意的
Chandler wouldn't mind if I opened just one present.
你觉得这是什么
What do you think it is?
是一面小镜子 只要你一照...
A little mirror that, when you look into it...
就会发现自己变成了老太婆
...you see yourself as an old woman.
是个迷你盐罐
A tiny salt shaker!
天啊  是用来装迷你盐的
Oh, my God, for tiny salt!
-好吧  拆礼物真好玩  -是啊
- Oh, wow! Okay. Well, that was fun. - Oh, yeah.
我会等钱德勒回来
Okay, I'll just wait for Chandler
-一起拆其他礼物  -好
- to open up the rest of them. - Okay.
但这只是调味瓶组的一部分
Although, you know, this is part of a salt-and-pepper set.
它只能算半份礼物  你觉得呢
It may just count as only half a present. What do you think?
如果这是一套的
I guess it's okay to open one more
再拆开一样应该没关系  就这个吧
if it's part of a set. It's probably this one.
或是这个
Or this one!
你感觉怎样  晨吐了吗
How are you feeling? Got any morning sickness?
男生们还不知道吧
The guys don't know yet, do they?
乔伊跟罗斯什么都不知道
No, Joey and Ross don't know anything.
钱德勒还以为是菲比怀孕了
And Chandler still thinks Phoebe's pregnant.
没错  钱德勒还以为是我怀孕了
That's right. Chandler does still think I'm pregnant.
他没问我感觉如何 也没帮我提袋子
He hasn't asked me how I'm feeling or offered to carry my bags.
我真替跟他在一起的女人觉得难过
I feel bad for the woman who ends up with him.
我是指在你之后的女人
After you, of course.
别担心  你只需要再假装怀孕几小时
Don't worry. I promise you only have to be pregnant for a few more hours
因为今天我要告诉孩子他爸了
...because I'm telling the father today.
他就住在这栋公寓吗
Is it someone in the building?
是一楼那个高个子吗
That tall guy on the first floor?
才不是呢
No!
怎么  我觉得他很帅啊
What? I think he's cute.
那你可以去怀他的孩子
Then you have his baby.
相信我  我正在努力
Believe me, I'm trying.
这种感觉真奇怪  你今天就要告诉这个男人
It's so weird. You're gonna tell this guy today...
而他完全不知道会发生什么事
...and he has no idea what's gonna happen.
你马上就要敲开他的门
Yeah. You're just gonna knock on his door
永远改变他的生活
and change his life forever.
你就像艾德·麦马汉
You're like Ed McMahon,
只是手上没有拿大额支票
except without the big check.
也缺乏原始的性吸引力
Or the raw sexual magnetism.
对  这确实是个大消息
Yeah, well, I guess it is pretty big news.
大消息  这可是个天大的消息
Pretty big? It's huge!
天啊  这个男人什么都不知道
God, this guy doesn't have a clue.
他走在街上心想
He's just walking down the street thinking,
"我跟瑞秋·格林做爱了  我太帅了"
"I had sex with Rachel Greene. I rock!"
然后  砰  他突然当了爸爸  一切都变了
Then, bam! He's a father, everything's different.
除非他真的想当爸爸
It's only different if he wants it to be.
我不会对他提出任何要求
I'm not gonna ask him for anything.
他还是得做出重大的决定
Okay, then. He still has this huge decision to make.
现在他边走边想
Now he's walking around thinking,
"我要当爸爸吗"  然后  砰
"Do I want to be a dad?" Then, bam!
这次怎么了
What was that "bam"?
我不知道  他可能是被公车撞了
I don't know. He's hit by a bus, or something.
乔伊  如果跟你上过床的女人
Joey, what would you do if someone you slept with
告诉你她怀孕了  你会怎么办
told you she was pregnant?
谁打电话过来了
Who called here?
她听起来像金发美女吗
Did she sound blond?
她有口音吗  我得去打个电话
Did she have an accent? I gotta make a call.
我就不该进太阳眼镜屋的
Should have never walked into that Sunglass Hut!
不是你  你没有让任何人怀孕
Joey, Joey. It's not you! You didn't get anybody pregnant.
你为什么要那样子吓我
Why would you scare me like that?
发生了什么事
What the hell's going on?
有人怀孕了吗
Is somebody pregnant?
对  我怀孕了
Oh, yeah! That's me.
天啊  菲比 你要生孩子了
Oh, my God, Pheebs! You're gonna have a baby?
对  天啊  我要生孩子了
Yes, I am. Oh, my God, I'm gonna have a baby!
等一下  孩子他爸是谁
Wait a minute, who's the father?
你不认识他  那不重要
You don't know him. It's not important.
他不希望跟我或孩子扯上关系
He wants nothing to do with me or the baby.
这家伙是谁
Who is this guy? Who is he?
我要找到他  痛扁他一顿
Because I will track him down and kick his ass!
-大卫·林恩  -大卫·林恩
- David Linn. - David Linn!
大卫`林恩  大卫`林恩
David Linn. David Linn!
谁是大卫·林恩
Who's David Linn?
我在健身房认识的人  他有点烦人
Some guy from my gym. Little annoying.
-钱德勒  -你找到即可拍了吗
- Chandler? - Did you find the cameras?
-没有  你呢  -我找到了
- No. Did you? - Yes.
所以我才趴在桌底下  庆祝这一幸事
That's why I'm under the table, celebrating.
我去失物招领中心问过管理员
I checked in the lost and found. I talked to the manager.
没有人捡到即可拍
No one's turned them in.
这下可好了  今天只有那些即可拍
This is great. Those cameras were the only thing
才能让莫妮卡打起精神来  她心情很低落
that was gonna cheer Monica up today. She's really depressed.
你们刚刚结婚  她为什么心情不好
You guys just got married. Why is she so depressed?
我卯足了劲不去问她那个问题
All my energy is going into not asking that question.
不敢相信我给搞砸了
I can't believe I screwed this up!
我很遗憾  兄弟
I'm sorry, man.
我有个点子  你们就是在这个宴会厅请的客
Here's a thought. This is the same ballroom.
这里有乐队  等一下会有很多人盛装前来
There's a band. There's gonna be plenty of dressed-up people.
你是说我们可以一跳解千愁
Are you suggesting we dance our troubles away?
不  我是说我们到礼品店买一些即可拍
No, no, no, I'm saying we buy more of these at the gift shop...
换上礼服拍几张照片
...throw our tuxes back on and take a few pictures.
我们只要不拍到任何人的脸就行
All we have to make sure not to get anybody's faces.
你是认真的吗
Are you serious?
我是想到在家等你的新娘
I'm just thinking about your new bride at home, okay?
你想在携手共度一生的第一天就让她失望吗
Do you want to start your life together by letting her down?
你真的要给我关于婚姻的建议吗
Marriage advice? Really?
我是在告诉你  这看起来很像你的婚宴现场
I'm telling you, this looks exactly like your wedding.
连这些花都是一样吧
Aren't these the same flowers?
我不知道  花是莫妮卡挑的
I don't know. Monica picked out the flowers.
-椅子呢  -也是她挑的
- What about the chairs? - She picked out those too.
-那会场布置呢  -她挑的
- How about the place settings? - That was her.
-你做了什么  -我负责看好照相机
- What did you do? - I was in charge of the cameras.
去礼品店吧
Gift shop?
-你说了吗  -还没有
- Did you do it yet? - Not yet.
那么你在这里做什么  你准备要说了吗
Then what are you doing here? Are you about to do it?
-是甘瑟吗  -不是
- Is it Gunther? - No.
不是甘瑟
Phoebe, it's not Gunther!
谢天谢地  还好宝宝不会随他的头发
Thank God. Because that hair on a baby?
孩子他爸不在这里
Phoebe, the father is not here, okay?
我还没有告诉他  我现在根本没办法告诉他
I haven't told him yet. I don't think I can tell him at all now.
-为什么  -让我想想
- Why not? - I don't konw. Let me think.
我在街上边走边想
I was walking down the street, thinking,
"我今天要告诉孩子他爸了"  然后  砰
"I'm gonna tell the father." And then, bam!
你被公车撞了吗
Bus?
不  是你  我被你吓到了
No, you! Phoebe, you freaked me out.
你一直在提醒我这是件大事
You kept saying how huge this all is.
但这的确是件大事
But it is huge.
我知道  但我只是在想这对我来说有多重要
I know. But I was just thinking about how huge it was for me.
我根本没去想这对孩子他爸来说有多重要
I didn't even go to how huge it'll be for the father.
你想得太多了
You're thinking about this way too much.
就直接告诉他  把事情做个了断
Just tell him and get it over with.
就像撕掉创可贴一样  越快越不痛  你看
It's like ripping off this Band-Aid, quick and painless. Watch.
天杀的...
Oh, mother of...!
看吧
See?
要拆礼物了吗
Are we opening presents?
不  我根本不该拆礼物
No. I shouldn't have even opened these.
乔伊  我控制不了自己
Joey, I am out of control!
你得帮我一个忙
Joey, you have to do me a favor.
不论我说什么  不论我做什么
No matter what I say, no matter what I do...
拜托  不要让我再拆礼物了  好吗
...please, do not let me open another present. Okay?
好
Okay.
-再给我一个礼物  -好
- Give me one more. - Okay.
很好  你来了  菲比  听我说
Oh, good, you're here. Pheebs? Listen...
-坐下  我要告诉你一件事  -好吧
- Sit down, I got something I wanna say. - All right.
外面的世界很可怕
It's a scary world out there,
特别是对单亲妈妈来说
especially for a single mom.
我一直觉得你我之间有种特殊的联系
I've always felt that you and I have a special bond.
所以...
So...
菲比·布菲  你愿意嫁给我吗
Phoebe Buffay, will you marry me?
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
-乔伊  -我愿意嫁给你
- Joey. - Oh, yeah, I'll marry you.
你不能嫁给他
You can't marry him!
小姐  你的风光之日过去了  这次轮到我了
Hey, lady, your day's over. It's my turn.
-菲比  -她为什么不能嫁给我
- Phoebe. - Why can't she marry me?
我可以  我也愿意
I can and I will.
她没有怀孕
She's not pregnant.
是瑞秋怀孕了
It's Rachel. Rachel's the one who's pregnant, okay?
天啊
Oh, my God!
九个月后你生不出孩子
Phoebe, I think he'd notice when you didn't have a baby
他会发现的
in nine months!
他可是乔伊
It's Joey!
我爱你
I love you.
等一下  我不敢相信瑞秋怀孕了
Wait, I can't believe it! Rachel's pregnant?
孩子他爸是谁
Who's the father?
我们不知道
We don't know.
不知道是不是那个家伙
I wonder if it's that dude.
-你知道有这么个人  -对
- There's a dude? - Yeah.
是谁呢
Who is it?
大约一个月前  这家伙跟瑞秋共度春宵
About a month ago this guy spent the night with Rachel.
我没有看到是谁  但是...
I didn't see who it was, but...
他把故事讲完了吗
Was that story over?
那家伙留下了这个
The guy left this.
天啊  我知道孩子他爸是谁了
Oh, my God! I know who the father is.
就不能把故事讲完吗
People have got to finish their stories.
打扰一下  你能帮我们拍照吗
Excuse me, could you take a picture of us?
没问题
Of course.
你能帮我们照一张吗
Would you take one of us?
没问题
Yeah, sure.
咔嚓
Click.
-我没有听到快门声  -我听到了
- It didn't click. - I heard it. I heard it.
但闪光灯没亮
But there was no flash.
你为什么不帮我们拍照
Why won't you take our picture?
好  我来帮你们拍
Oh, yeah. I'll take your picture.
你的手指挡到镜头了
Your finger was covering the lens.
你是安瑟·亚当斯吗  快滚吧
Who are you, Ansel Adams? Get out of here!
之前吓到你了  我真的很过意不去
Look, I feel really bad about how I freaked you out before...
所以我打电话把孩子他爸叫到这里见你
...so I called the father and asked the father to meet you here
你可以告诉他事实  去吧
so you could tell him. Go!
什么  等一下
What? Wait a minute.
你怎么知道孩子他爸是谁
Phoebe, how do you even know who the father is?
或许有时候我会装傻
I may play the fool at times...
但事实上我是个永不放弃的金发美女
but I'm more than a pretty blond girl with an ass that won't quit.
我相信这是孩子他爸的衣服
I believe this belongs to the father of your baby...
天啊
Oh, God.
他就在里面吗
He's in there right now?
你可以转身离开  或是长痛不如短痛
You can turn around, or you can go rip the Band-Aid off.
你打算怎么做
What do you want to do?
-我们把事情做个了断吧  -你确定
- Let's rip. - Are you sure?
-菲比  -好吧  抱歉
- Phoebe! - Okay. Sorry.
瑞秋
Hey, Rach.
你到台上去吧
Why don't you go up on-stage.
-我来拍张你致辞的照片  -好
- I'll get a picture of you doing the speech. - Okay, okay.
1995款别克利萨布尔的车主
Will the owner of a 1995 Buick LeSabre
请跟前台联络  你的车就要被拖走了
please see the front desk? Your car is about to be towed.
那是我的车
That's my car!
-1995款的利萨布尔  -对
- A '95 LeSabre? - Yes.
-绿色的利萨布尔  -对
- A green LeSabre? - Yes!
抱歉  我是说蓝色的利萨布尔
I'm sorry, I meant a blue LeSabre.
对  我的车是蓝绿色的
Yes, green-blue.
快去把车移开吧
Well, go. Go move it!
准备好拍最后一张照片了吗
Okay. Ready for the last picture?
-好  -拍完马上就跑
- Yeah. - Get ready to run.
恭贺新婚
Congratulations on your wedding.
这是怎么一回事
So, what's this about?
瑞秋有事要告诉你
Rachel has something she wants to tell you.
我敢肯定这是你的红毛衣
And I believe that this is your red sweater.
不  这才是我的红毛衣
No, this is my red sweater.
不是吧
Oh, no.
有人要喝咖啡吗
Could I get anyone a coffee?
或是毒药  没有吗  只有我要喝  好吧
Or poison? No? Just for me? Okay.
发生了什么事  瑞秋
What's going on, Rach?
没事  菲比搞错了
Nothing. Phoebe kind of made a mistake.
但你的确常穿那件毛衣
But you do wear that sweater a lot.
你这是在玩什么"大冒险"吗
Are you involved in some kind of dare?
事实上我很高兴能接到菲比的电话
I'm actually glad Phoebe called.
我知道我们会分手是因为你觉得我太幼稚
I know we broke up because you thought I was immature enough,
但我已经长大了
but I've really grown up.
我觉得我们应该复合
I think we should get back together.
时机不对
It's just not the right time.
-时机非常恰当  -好吧
- It is the right time. - Okay.
我做了万全的准备
I'm ready for more.
-泰格  -来吧  瑞秋我们再试一次
- Tag. - Come on, Rach. Let's give it another try.
我怀孕了
I'm having a baby.
-你可以走了  -谢谢
- You can go. - Thank you.
我不知道这些礼物怎么会是打开的
I don't know how any of these got opened!
你拆开了所有的礼物
You opened them all?
我知道  我太不靠谱了
I know, I know I am a terrible person.
钱德勒再也不会相信我了
Chandler's never gonna trust me with anything ever again.
你拆开了我爸妈的礼物
You got my parents' gift.
那是什么
Yeah. What is that?
应该是跟意大利腊肠有关的东西
I don't know. I think it does something to salami.
-情况如何  -泰格怎么说
- How'd it go? - What did Tag say?
泰格不是孩子他爸  乔伊竟然知道了
Tag is not the father. And Joey knows now?
我知道了  瑞秋  我为你感到高兴
I do, Rach, I do. And I am so happy for you.
你竟然没想要解开我的胸罩
Wow, you didn't even try to unook my bra.
你还打算要告诉孩子他爸吗
So are you ever gonna tell whoever it is?
我会的  我只是不想今晚告诉他
I will. I'm just not up for it tonight.
不论这家伙怎么说
Rach, no matter what this guy says,
你都不会独自面对这一切
I want you to know you're not gonna be alone in this.
-是吗  -不  听着...
- I'm not? - No. Listen, I...
外面的世界很可怕
It's a scary world out there,
特别是对单亲妈妈来说
especially for a single mom.
我一直觉得我跟你之间有种特殊的联系
I've always felt like you and I have this special bond, you know?
-瑞秋·格林  你愿意嫁给我吗  -什么
- Rachel Greene, will you marry me? - What?
-什么  -什么
- What? - What?!
-菲比  把戒指还给我  -不要
- Pheebs, give me the ring back. - No!
乔伊  你真的很体贴
No, Joey, you're so sweet, you're so, so sweet, honey.
但我现在不需要丈夫
But I'm not looking for a husband.
我了解
I understand.
失陪了  我想去躺一下
Well, if you'll excuse me, I'm going to go and lie down.
我不能说我不心痛
I can't say that didn't hurt.
但我会原谅你  乔伊·崔比安尼
But I'll take you back, Joey Tribbiani.
听着  我只是说...
Yeah, Pheebs. Listen, about that, I only offered...
-意大利腊肠用具  -是啊
- Ooh, a Salami Buddy! - There you go!
-我们回来了  -太棒了
- We're back! - Great.
我们待在厨房吧  待在厨房就好了
We're hanging in the kitchen. Let's stay in the kitchen.
现在是看照片时间  -你一定会喜欢的
- It's picture time. - You're gonna love these.
这是罗斯的照片
Here's a picture of Ross.
这是我
And that's me.
这是我跟罗斯
And that's me and Ross.
这是我们第一次以新婚夫妻身份接吻的照片
And here's a picture of our first kiss as a married couple.
那张照片真的很棒
Wow, that is a great picture. Yeah!
有意思的是  我在我们的行李里
And interesting, because I found the cameras
找到了即可拍
in one of our bags.
我没想到会这样
Didn't see that coming.
这不是我们第一次接吻的照片
Okay. So this isn't a picture of our first kiss...
但这的确是我跟这位女士第一次接吻的照片
...but it is a picture of my first kiss with this lady.
从你脸上的表情看来
Which, by the look on your face,
我相信你会记得这个画面  所以我不必...
I'm sure you'll remember, so there's no need...
我会拿真的底片去洗
How about I'll take the real pictures to get developed right now.
-好主意  -好
- That'd be a good idea. - Okay.
你不管我  自己拆了所有礼物
You opened all the presents without me?
我们说好要一起拆的
I thought we were supposed to do that together.
你吻了另一个女人
You kissed another woman?!
-我们扯平了  -好吧
- Call it even? - Okay.
我要把花插到花瓶里
I'm gonna go get these in some water.
那是你从人家婚礼上偷的吗
You stole those from these people's wedding?
不  这是酒店大厅的花
No, I took them from the hotel lobby.
他们以为能多收我黄片
They think they can charge me for some dirty movie...
还有一袋糖果的钱  我一定要讨回公道
...and a bag of Mashuga Nuts, they got another thing coming!
我的毛衣
Hey, my sweater!
我找这件毛衣找了一个月
I've been looking for this for, like a month.
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
-你好吗  -我很好  好久不见
- Hey, how you doing? - Good. Long time no see.
-我喜欢你的毛衣  -我也是
- Like your sweater. - Right back at you.
瑞秋的事真的太疯狂了
It's crazy about Rachel.
她一直都疯疯癫癫的
Well, she's one crazy lady.
到底是谁的呢
So whose is it?
我不知道  应该是个意大利人吧
I don't know, some Italian guy.
少来了  看你自己的标签去
Come on, read your own label.
后会有期  他真是个怪人
See you later. He is so weird.